<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dr. Skin</string>
    <string name="rules_button_text">Let\'s get into it!</string>
    <string name="accept_rules_text">I have read the rules.</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="appointments">Appointments</string>
    <string name="rules"><font color="#00FAEB">About.</font>\n\nThe app is using TensorFlow model to help detect and track your skin health status.\n\nBlack list of diseases you might want to check and get rid of:\n\n<font color="#CF3B2C">•</font> Acne\n<font color="#CF3B2C">•</font> Skin allergy\n<font color="#CF3B2C">•</font> Nail fungus\n<font color="#CF3B2C">•</font> Hair loss\n\n<font color="#00FAEB">Features.</font>\n\nWith this app you can:\n\n<font color="#00FAEB">•</font> Using phone camera or media store you can easily check your skin for having some disease.\n<font color="#00FAEB">•</font> Read useful info and tips.\n<font color="#00FAEB">•</font> Save your diagnosis as a history item.\n<font color="#00FAEB">•</font> Need to visit a doctor? Using the app - make an appointment and attach the history.\n<font color="#00FAEB">•</font> Track and manage your therapy.\n\nStay healthy with us!</string>
    <string name="take_photo">Take a photo</string>
    <string name="acne_info">Acne is a common skin condition that affects most people at some point. It causes spots, oily skin and sometimes skin that\'s hot or painful to touch.\n\nAcne is most commonly linked to the changes in hormone levels during puberty, but can start at any age.\nCertain hormones cause the grease-producing glands next to hair follicles in the skin to produce larger amounts of oil (abnormal sebum).\n\nAcne most commonly develops on the:\n• face – this affects almost everyone with acne\n• back – this affects more than half of people with acne\n• chest – this affects about 15% of people with acne\n\nSeveral creams, lotions and gels for treating spots are available to buy from pharmacies.\n\nProducts containing a low concentration of benzoyl peroxide may be recommended, but be careful as this can bleach clothing.\n\nIf your acne is severe or appears on your chest and back, it may need to be treated with antibiotics or stronger creams that are only available on prescription.</string>
    <string name="normal_skin_info">Sometimes it\’s hard to know what your skin really needs to be as healthy as possible. Every day we\’re bombarded by marketing hype for various skin care and cosmetic products, as well as advice from social media influencers and other beauty gurus.\n\nSo, what does the research say your skin actually needs? What helps and what doesn\’t in the quest for clear, radiant skin?\n\n• Wash your face twice a day\n• Use a mild cleanser\n• Apply an acne-fighting agent\n• Get plenty of sleep\n• Don\’t pick at your skin\n• Relax\n\n Focusing on certain lifestyle factors, like quality sleep, a healthy diet, and stress management, can make a difference to your skin, too.\n\nIf you\’ve tried several types of treatments for your acne and nothing works, make an appointment with a dermatologist. They may prescribe treatments like antibiotics or prescription medications to help clear your skin. If you don\’t already have a dermatologist, our Healthline FindCare tool can help you connect to physicians in your area.</string>
    <string name="nail_fungus_info">Nail fungus is a common condition that begins as a white or yellow spot under the tip of your fingernail or toenail. As the fungal infection goes deeper, nail fungus may cause your nail to discolor, thicken and crumble at the edge. It can affect several nails.\n\nIf your condition is mild and not bothering you, you may not need treatment. If your nail fungus is painful and has caused thickened nails, self-care steps and medications may help. But even if treatment is successful, nail fungus often comes back.\n\nNail fungus is also called onychomycosis (on-ih-koh-my-KOH-sis). When fungus infects the areas between your toes and the skin of your feet, it\'s called athlete\'s foot (tinea pedis).\n\nYou may have nail fungus if one or more of your nails are:\n• Thickened\n• Whitish to yellow-brown discoloration\n• Brittle, crumbly or ragged\n• Distorted in shape\n• A dark color, caused by debris building up under your nail\n• Smelling slightly foul\n\nNail fungus can affect fingernails, but it\'s more common in toenails.\n\nYou may want to see a physician if self-care steps haven\'t helped and the nail becomes increasingly discolored, thickened or deformed. Also see a doctor if you have diabetes and think you\'re developing nail fungus.</string>
    <string name="skin_allergy_info">A skin allergy is when skin becomes irritated because the immune system reacted to something that is usually harmless. This is called an allergic reaction. An allergic reaction can cause rash, itching, burning, redness, bumps, hives, and swelling. Many different allergens can cause a reaction. Below are some of the most common allergic skin conditions:\n\n• Atopic dermatitis\n• Allergic contact dermatitis\n• Urticaria\n• Angioedema\n\nThe symptoms of a skin allergy vary depending on the type of reaction:\n\n• Eczema causes an itchy, scaly, red, dry rash, especially on the face, hands, elbows, and knees. Sometimes eczema weeps clear fluid as well.\n• Allergic contact dermatitis causes a rash that may be itchy but is often painful. The rash may have both raised bumps and blisters. The reaction may happen right away or it may be up to 48 hours after your skin was exposed to whatever is causing it to react.\n• Hives are raised, flat, itchy bumps that may also be tender. Hives are a sign of a potentially serious allergic reaction.\n• Angioedema is a type of swelling. For example, angioedema on the eyelid can cause your eye to be swollen shut. When it happens in the throat, it is an emergency because the swelling makes it hard to breathe.\n\nA skin allergy is a skin condition where the immune systems reacts strongly to an allergen. The reaction can cause irritation, rashes, swelling, or hives. The cause of the allergy depends on the condition and the allergen.\n\nTreatment for skin allergy varies depending on the problem and the allergen, but usually includes two approaches:\n\n• Avoid the allergen, if it is known.\n• Use medicines, creams, and other strategies to relieve the itching, swelling, or pain.</string>
    <string name="hair_loss_info">Hair loss (alopecia) can affect just your scalp or your entire body, and it can be temporary or permanent. It can be the result of heredity, hormonal changes, medical conditions or a normal part of aging. Anyone can lose hair on their head, but it\'s more common in men.\n\nBaldness typically refers to excessive hair loss from your scalp. Hereditary hair loss with age is the most common cause of baldness. Some people prefer to let their hair loss run its course untreated and unhidden. Others may cover it up with hairstyles, makeup, hats or scarves. And still others choose one of the treatments available to prevent further hair loss or restore growth.\n\nBefore pursuing hair loss treatment, talk with your doctor about the cause of your hair loss and treatment options.\n\nSigns and symptoms of hair loss may include:\n• Gradual thinning on top of head.\n• Circular or patchy bald spots.\n• Sudden loosening of hair.\n• Full-body hair loss.\n• Patches of scaling that spread over the scalp.\n\nSee your doctor if you are distressed by persistent hair loss in you or your child and want to pursue treatment. For women who are experiencing a receding hairline (frontal fibrosing alopecia), talk with your doctor about early treatment to avoid significant permanent baldness.\n\nAlso talk to your doctor if you notice sudden or patchy hair loss or more than usual hair loss when combing or washing your or your child\'s hair. Sudden hair loss can signal an underlying medical condition that requires treatment.</string>
    <string name="no_history">No history items yet.</string>
    <string name="no_appointments">No appointment items yet.</string>
    <string name="probability">Probability: %.1f</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>